[Netero] Do not underestimate
humans, Meruem.
[Meruem] What is this?
[Netero] Meruem, King of the Ants,
within the human heart.
[tense music playing]
From the very beginning,
checkmate was yours.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
but despite this, it also
proved surprisingly lethal.
to mass-produce these bombs
in short time,
making it a favorite among dictatorships.
This, along with the peculiar shape
of the fallout cloud,
earned this bomb the name
"Miniature Rose,"
or the "Poor Man's Rose."
which effectively banned
the bomb's production.
[imperceptible]
However, over 80% of countries
rejected the proposal
to discard the existing Roses
that had already been produced.
This means that even today
in far too many countries,
hundreds upon thousands of seeds
still wait silently
for their chance to bloom.
"Were humans really
so different from Ants?"
-[bomb explodes]
-[both gasp]
[narrator] A plume of smoke
rose in the distance,
At the same time, outside of the palace,
Pouf's segment found itself
looking Knuckle in the eye.
[gasps]
[narrator] After his experience
with Youpi,
Knuckle hoped that he would be able
to reach a similar understanding
with Pouf,
but his hopes, faint as they were,
were utterly shattered.
[sighs]
The King can just wave his hand
and turn all of them into evil spawn.
[Knuckle] I see.
Pouf's real body must have learned
that something happened to the King.
Then the segment's face transformed,
revealing its true nature.
Did the Chairman defeat the King?
Well, I suppose
it doesn't matter either way.
[narrator] When he looked
at Pouf's face,
Is everyone okay?
[grunting]
[gasps]
[wind blowing]
This is brutal.
It only took them 30 minutes
to wreck the whole place.
That was close.
-[Killua] Ikalgo.
-[gasps]
[gasps] Killua!
[dramatic music playing]
It's Palm.
I see. I'm glad you're here.
You finally made it back to us.
Now do you remember the plan?
I'll take you to the capital by car.
No. It turns out she wants to stay.
Well, she ought to be pretty useful
in a fight at least.
[Gon] I'll wait right here for one hour.
[Killua] And once he's made up his mind,
he won't budge.
But to be honest,
that situation is ideal.
is try to stay out of his way.
Well, sure, but what if he--
Yeah. Yeah, I know.
If Gon's in trouble,
we'll all rush in to help him out.
Let's just be ready
for whatever happens with him.
[Ikalgo] Oh, I get it.
So that's what staying means, huh?
Even if Gon uses all the power
he has right now,
it won't be enough.
He still won't be able to beat Pitou.
In fact, even if all three of us join him,
Pitou still has us outmatched
and knows that just as well as we do.
[Killua] Okay. Let's go.
[Knuckle] We separated the King
and the Royal Guards
Do we stop or keep going?
[tense music playing]
You're done, right?
[Neferpitou gasps]
[Neferpitou] Why did he say that?
I may have relaxed a bit,
and if he noticed,
then in that instant…
I have to kill him.
No matter the cost.
I must… for the King's sake.
Did he sense my bloodlust then?
It's time for us to go to Peijing.
It'll be a lot faster if we run there.
[Komugi whimpering]
What happened to me?
[Komugi] I… I'm sorry!
I'm so rude. Am I interrupting?
[narrator] Pitou was close enough
to decapitate Gon with one arm,
[gasps]
Oh, and if Pitou tries to run away,
[Neferpitou gasps]
[whimpering]
[Gon] Thanks a lot, Knuckle,
but it's okay.
For some reason, I trust Pitou.
[gasps]
So do me a favor, Knuckle.
Take care of that girl for us
until we see Kite.
[gasps]
Uh, are you guys talking about me?
[dramatic music playing]
[gasps]
[Neferpitou] Does he seriously plan to…
[Knuckle] Use the girl as a hostage?
I promise you that.
So I guess that means, for now,
you're just gonna have to trust me too.
Right, Pitou?
[whimpers]
It's fine. Leave the rest to Pitou and me.
It's okay. That was always
the plan, wasn't it?
Truth is, I feel better
after hearing what he's doing.
How many bloodbaths
did they have to endure
to start thinking like that?
Uh…
[Palm] It's all right.
Now that I've laid my eyes on Gon,
if something happens,
I'll know about it immediately.
[Killua] Besides it's not like Pitou
is gonna abandon her,
which means that Gon is safe for now.
[all sigh]
[Komugi] What's happening?
I don't understand what's going on here.
[fire crackling]
that it melted the rock into magma,
leaving a scene resembling
the mouth of an active volcano,
a perpetual cloud of black smoke
driving all life away.
[Shaiapouf gasping]
Hey, Pouf!
[gasps]
It's possible the explosion
may have sent the King flying.
You know, I was wrong.
We'll kill every one of them…
by the King's side.
Not a single one will be spared.
[gasping]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[groans]
[imperceptible]
[narrator] Youpi's howl was not a sign
of good things to come,
and before he even realized it himself,
[imperceptible]
[suspenseful music playing]
[closing theme music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Unparalleled Joy
and Unconditional Love."
[Killua] Yeah, I never ask
for anything in return.
[Gon] That's unconditional love.
[Killua] Unparalleled joy.